Stephan Benchemoul

+972544-522614 Phone: Location: Tel Aviv, Israel

Website: https://stephanbenchemoul.com/

Email: stephanbncml@gmail.com

Web Developer specializing in front-end and styling.

Creative thinker with passion for programming and code..

Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects.

Open to full time jobs or single projects.

EXPERIENCE

PWM 2021 - 2022

Full Stack developer

Web solutions for major tech companies.

Front-end developing using React with Mobx as state management.

Server written in Node Js with micro services using Single store as database.

Writing unit tests with React test library and Jest.

Storybook for reusable components, and Sass for styling.

More technologies -Figma, Material / Mui, i18 Translate, Highcharts, Jenkins and more...

Moveo Group 2020-2021

Full Stack web developer

Web solutions outsourcing.

Building a full Culinary App using Angular for Front-end developing.

Server written in Node Js. using Mongo DB as database.

Deployment with AWS.

More technologies - Github CI/CD, apiDOC, Docker, Puppeteer, Styled Components, Sass, Zeplin, Typescript and more..

Building a design system using React, Mui Components, Sass and Redux Toolkit.

Inception 2019 - 2020

QA

QA for Bookful book app

Self Employed 2008 - 2019

Sound Designer / Music Production / Music Production Teacher

EDUCATION

John Bryce 2019 - 2020

Full Stack Web developer Course Completed with honors.

S.A.E Australia 2006-2008

Sound Engineering Bachelor degree

LANGUAGES

French (Professional working proficiency), English (Full professional proficiency), Hebrew (Native)